Rosewood Academy
The battle royale: a special
program at Rosewood Academy.
Testing Ground No. 2
A valuable exercise where each student uses
the fruits of their training to compete.
Or at least it was supposed to be...
Parent's gone and won all by himself!
Have no fear! I'm still here!
With my drill lance's Absolute Defense!
Ah, that move is a real pain in the neck.
Do your best, Leonard!
You're the last one standing!
Avenge us!
Would it hurt to lose every
once in a while, Blade?
Take the loss! Take the loss!
Why am I the bad guy here?
That is because almost everyone
here was defeated by you, Master.
Ah, well, I guess that makes sense.
Leonard!
Please give it all you've got!
Even if we may both fall here...
I swear to bring victory upon your name,
my lord, Earnest Flaming!
Leonard! You can do it!
C'mon! Anna, cheer him on!
Huh? Leonard hasn't been knocked out yet?
Why's he of all people still standing?
Blade's the kind who leaves
his carrots for last.
Oh, he puts off the things he hates?
Leonard! Get back on your feet!
Cut it out with that skeleton!
Here I go!
Knew it.
We're talking about Leonard here.
Say what you will, but I still have my lord!
I can finally eat now!
Hey, let's go grab some food.
Thank you.
I really don't stand a chance against you.
I look in your eyes, and I'm met with
A brand-new me and dream
Bravery? Naturally?
Polar opposites within the heart
But, you know, wanting to have both
That's the saga of human nature
Oh no, don't mind me
Go ahead, and so on, you know the rest
A little more? Wait, even harder?!
Going overboard much?
Those selfish emotions deep down
Bringing them to light is
what friendship's about
Spending adolescence duking it out with pals
I don't wanna lose
We're off to the cutting edge moment
Fight with best friends, and leave no regrets
You should laugh, since
you look best with a smile
On the ropes?! No matter
what we face, et cetera
Just sit back and enjoy it
Whatever may come, I'll
be here to protect you
Episode 9
The Superorganism Suppression Committee
Rosewood Academy Residence Hall
Maria's Room, Bath
Hm... You of all people...
Mao.
Oh, I was just a bit surprised.
Leonard's Room
Well... I had already realized it.
Blade really is so strong.
There will always be someone better.
I know that's only obvious.
If I can defeat Blade,
I'm sure that the Empress...
Can I defeat him?
That's right! I should begin
by repairing my weapon!
Rosewood Academy
Courtyard
Are you okay with this?
Is something the matter, Maria?
You want to defeat Blade, but you can't.
You lost to him, but you're
calmly laughing it off.
Are you okay just staying like this?
You wouldn't understand.
I can't say I do.
I don't want to be behind Blade.
What I want is to stand by his side.
It's frustrating to lose to him,
though I've never actually faced him.
But I swear that one day, I'll stand at his side
because of my own ability.
Could it be that you...
Ah, no! I-I didn't mean it in that way!
It's like Mao always says!
I shall be the one to kill you!
It's like that!
A declaration of rivalry!
Do you want to kill Blade?
Huh?!
N-No, I don't want to do that at all!
I'm sure Mao doesn't really
want to kill him, either!
Huh? That part is true?
Seriously?!
I've come to my senses.
You said all that to try and
light a fire under me.
When I saw you trying to put
yourself down compared to Blade...
I couldn't bear to see you cast aside
your desire to rival him, and defeat him.
I'm sorry!
I was being selfish.
Please, raise your head.
I should be the one thanking you.
I must defeat him at any cost.
Or else my lord will not
see fit to look my way.
I'm rooting for you!
I'll be rooting for you, as well.
Yes!
Hold it right there for just one moment!
Rooting this, rooting that.
Give me a break.
So it amounts to nothing more than idealism?
How laughable.
Utterly preposterous.
Pretend to be friends all you want!
Live up your youth all you want!
Heck, be as idealistic as you want!
However!
Do you think you can beat that
superorganism like that?!
Huh? W-Well, um...
Hm?
I don't mean to criticize you.
But if you seriously want
to take that thing down,
I can lend a hand.
Yes, with a realistic plan
instead of idealism!
Using this gray matter of mine!
Thanks, um...
Who are you?
Eliza!
Heaven and earth alike shall not
tolerate this transcended being!
First Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Chairman: Leonard
I thank you all for gathering
here on this day.
Empress: Earnest
Hey, why are you the chairman?
Gray Matter: Eliza
More like, Empress, why are you here?
Demon King's Daughter: Maria
Because this meeting
is about defeating Blade!
I want to beat him to a bloody pulp!
Guardian: Iona
Eradication is my specialty.
Whatever, let's just get it over with!
Assassin: Kassim
Swordsman: Clay
Yeah!
Though we share not the day of our births,
we swear here an oath of fellowship,
to challenge the transcended
one who defies logic—
What the heck does that mean?
Leonard!
Guts! You've got to show some guts!
Guts!
In other words!
All of us may have different motives,
but we all want to beat the superorganism!
Artificial Hero: Sophitia Femto
Baby Dragon: Cu Chulainn
I'm fine as long as Blade is happy.
Parent!
D-Does anyone here have
a specific plan in mind?
Healer: Claire
Spy: Yessica
Here!
Attack him in his sleep!
Poison him?
What? That's cowardly.
No, there's nothing cowardly about it.
In fact, wouldn't you say that being a
superorganism is about as cowardly as it gets?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm!
Illustrative Footage from Superorganism Simulator
We feeble humans are trying
to take on a superorganism!
It's only natural that we use whatever
methods are available to us!
I want to fight him fair and square.
I mean, Blade only ever uses a sword.
Why don't we challenge him with weapons
he'd be weak against, like lances or bows?
How's that different from attacking
him in his sleep or poisoning him?
Um, look...
What my lord is saying is that, well...
We should each face him with
whatever methods we see fit.
That's what she means, yep.
Y-Yeah, that's right!
That's what I meant to say!
Really?
Really!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Let us declare here our vow to defeat Blade,
and achieve victory without fail!
All in the name of suppressing
the superorganism in battle!
Rosewood Academy, Testing Ground No. 2
Super Drill Lance Mk. II
Let's fight fair and square!
Prepare yourself, Blade!
Here I go!
Second Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Thanks for letting me use your lance.
I'd just fixed this thing!
I'm up next!
Rosewood Academy Residence Hall, Late at Night
There's no point fighting
him when he's awake.
Blade's Bedroom
Okay, he's fast asleep!
Good, good...
Huh? Iona?
H-Hey, hey! Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
Third Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Hey, I thought we were on the same side.
That was an automatic function.
It's no good when he's asleep, either?
Then I'll take him on next!
Full Armor Drill Lance Perfect Pack Repair
With my renovated lance!
Blade!
Today is the day that I surpass you!
I really think you should just give up.
Enough talk!
Now face me in a fair fight!
Yeesh...
Fourth Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Duct tape ain't gonna cut it, huh?!
Mao and I will avenge the chairman!
Rosewood Academy Cafeteria
You're wide... open!
Have you forgotten that
I am the one who will kill—
In the middle of my introduction...
How cowardly...
Fifth Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Mao, you talk too much.
Testing Ground No. 2, Once Again
These are my only weapons.
Sixth Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
I'm fine as long as Blade is happy.
Rosewood Academy Cafeteria
Hi-yah!
Seventh Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
I knew it...
If we're together...
Testing Ground No. 2
We have nothing to fear!
Ah!
Look, over there, a naked lady!
So what if there's a naked lady?
Eighth Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Naked...
Lady...
Rosewood Academy Cafeteria
Prepare yourself, Parent!
It's too spicy!
It's good, you know?
Eek! I've tripped!
Operation Klutzy Dumbbell Accident
Whoopsie-daisy!
It didn't work.
Are you okay?
Go!
Rock-Paper-Scissors
Here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Shoot!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot!
Rosewood Academy Infirmary
Looks like tenosynovitis.
His wrists are way too strong!
You just suck at rock-paper-scissors.
So hot!
Endurance Contest
-Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
-Don't overdo it.
Endurance Contest 2
-No way, no way, no way, no way!
-Why'd you even try it?
My lord!
Endurance Contest 3
That lousy superorganism!
Eleventh Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
-Anna...
-That stupid moron!
-Let's calm down.
I know. Let's draw lots next.
We'll fill it with only losing lots,
and then Blade can...
Everyone, what was our original goal again?
I forgot!
Um...
Searching...
I want to defeat him!
Beat him to a bloody pulp!
And then make him say,
"Earnest, you're so strong!"
Argh!
That's right.
However, my lord...
In the search to be recognized,
rather than victory,
could it be that the very process
is what truly gives it meaning?
Leonard...
Wow, I never thought you'd talk back to Anna!
None of that matters if you don't win!
We need to beat him at least once!
I don't care what it is, as long as we win!
I just want to make him say uncle!
Argh!
"Say uncle"?
Say uncle.
In ancient language,
it means "to admit defeat."
In that case, it is possible.
I give, I give!
I admit defeat.
You're right! He said he gave up!
You're right!
The core of that strategy was that
we used Iona's life as a hostage.
Yes.
This means that if we take
hostages this time as well,
it should be possible to defeat Master.
Leonard? What's wrong?
Well... taking hostages...
We can defeat Blade!
I'll drink swamp water
if that's what it takes!
Got it?!
What unbridled passion!
I understand, my lord.
If that is your wish, I will spare no effort.
Let's do it, everyone!
My drill is burning up as it spins!
Huh...
Superorganism Suppression Committee, Operation Hostage
As you can see,
the medical approach here is fundamentally
different from that of healing magic.
Knowing how to heal the
human body can come in handy.
If you know how to heal it,
you also know how to injure it.
I know that!
Hey, Leonard and the others aren't here.
What?
Th-That's not true!
Oh, you know!
Those three had to go run an errand, I think!
What kind of errand?
You don't need to worry about that, Blade.
Nope.
Look here!
This place is under our control now!
Now!
What is that?
Ah! Those are...
Terrorists!
We're terrorists!
Terrorists?
It refers to people who use violence
to achieve their political goals.
Political?
Political!
I don't get it.
It means they're rowdy and rude!
I see.
I see!
Who are you people?!
Just shut up and do as we say!
Sorry, there's a reason for all this,
so please play along!
What?
If this doesn't concern you, get out!
Get out!
You need to stay in here!
Why? What's going on?
Can't you tell?!
They've taken our teacher hostage!
Hostage?
Hostage!
She's our hostage!
Oh, no! Help me, Blade!
Blade!
Huh? No fair.
You, there!
If you're going to take a hostage,
it should be me!
No, me!
Me, too! Me, too!
H-Hey.
Why did you come over here?!
No fair, I want in, too!
As a high-spec machine, I am
best suited to be held hostage.
My performance—
If we're talking high-spec,
it should be a genius like me!
I'm fine as long as Blade is happy.
Hey! You can't all come over here!
You're the one who came over first!
Boo! Boo!
I want Blade to save me, too!
As a beloved, high-spec character, I am...
I was the one who proposed the idea!
I'm fine as long as Blade is happy.
Must be nice to be young.
Sophie!
If you're fine with it,
then you get out of here!
I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's not fair!
What the heck are we doing?
We might have a chance with this!
Don't think about it too hard.
Master, please give me a command.
You can all live up your youth without me.
Ah, sure.
Oh, I've been taken hostage!
H-Help me!
Hey, Cu.
What is it, Parent?
What do you think the word "hostage" means?
Non-perishable food?
Non-perishable food, huh?
Eek, help me!
Those terrorists came here to accomplish
their political goals with violence, right?
Blade! Blade! Help me!
Political!
Hurry!
I'm so scared!
And they took the girls hostage,
to keep them as non-perishable food.
Huh? Blade?
Huh? What are you doing?
Blade, hurry!
Exactly!
You're so smart, Parent!
I see.
I don't get it at all.
Don't get it at all!
You nincompoop!
Blockhead!
Big fat dumb idiot!
Superorganism!
Your precious Earnest is in trouble!
Take things a little more seriously!
We're in trouble, too!
Just look at us!
My hands and feet and tentacles are tied.
Blade, are you happy?
I came up with this idea!
This is so funny!
Let's be serious here!
Eek! Help us!
Terrorists. Political. Violence.
Hostages. Non-perishable food.
I still don't get it.
Don't get it!
Stop it with the non-perishable food!
Are you okay with us being eaten?!
I am a good source of iron.
Eek! Help us!
H-Hurry up and surrender!
Hey, can I ask you something?
Wh-What?
What have you been doing this whole time?
Clay. Kassim. Leonard.
Wham bam boom!
You knew it was us?!
Since when?
Hm, from the start?
H-How?!
I mean, you can tell from the way
you walk and stuff, can't you?
Ah...
Damn it! Take a hint,
you lousy superorganism!
Damn it! This was so embarrassing!
So this is where it ends, huh?!
See, told you.
Damn it!
So? What were you planning to
do by taking the girls hostage?
We're still going?
Use them as non-perishable food, of course!
Really?!
Won't you reconsider it?
You shouldn't be eating your friends.
Wait, is Operation Hostage working?
In that case...
These boobs...
and these boobs...
belong to me!
You should know when to stop!
W-Well, Blade?
Give up? Do you give up?!
Why?
Not giving up, huh?
We know that you're weak against hostages.
When you fought Iona,
you couldn't lay a finger on her.
Come now, admit your defeat!
Admit your defeat!
That was true back then,
but it won't work this time.
Putting up a bold front.
What can you possibly do here?
My lord!
If I may.
Please do.
Ah! Help me!
He's going to kill me!
If I can't have you to myself,
then I'll be the one to...
Leonard...
His eyes are dead serious.
Give up? Give up yet?!
Give up yet?
Blade, what will you do?!
What will you do?
What will you do?!
I'll do this.
Huh?
Eh?
There, disarmed.
Wh-What did you do?!
I sliced up just your weapons
and armor with my slashes.
Penetrating Force Demonstration Video
It's an application of penetrating force.
M-My word!
Th-That's completely absurd!
This damn superorganism!
Now that it's come to this...
Now what?
We'll all attack him at once!
Oh? Hm? Oh?!
So what was all this, anyway?
Pretending to be terrorists.
I get it now!
So this was all make-believe!
This is my first time playing
a make-believe game!
Oh, did I do it right?
I don't know all the rules!
You did just fine.
Man, that's hilarious.
I think I broke something.
I broke some bones.
Me, too.
Master, you are wonderful
when you show no mercy.
Looks like we didn't stand a chance.
That's Parent for you!
I'm fine as long as Blade is happy.
I hate this, but...
Terrorists, will you
show up tomorrow as well?
No more!
I won't ever give up!
My lord!
Ladies and gentlemen!
334th Superorganism Suppression Committee Session
Let us begin our 334th session!
We're still doing this?
Of course!
We are the Superorganism
Suppression Committee!
Until we achieve our long-held dream,
we will never give up!
Exactly!
I see you in a new light, Leonard.
If it's for my lord...
He sure has it rough.
Does Anna not realize
Leonard's feelings for her?
Leonard, hang in there!
Um, can't we give it up?
No! This is our calling!
Indeed!
For man, as man alone,
to surpass the superorganism!
Let's work hard together.
I'll make him say it for sure!
"Earnest, you're amazing!"
Prepare yourself, Blade!
Together...
I'll do all I can to make Blade cry!
And say, "Earnest, I give up! Boo-hoo!"
Boo-hoo...
The chairman looks like he's
going to burst into tears.
Boo-hoo...
I feel so sorry for him.
Say uncle already, Blade!
Uncle!
Why are you saying it?!
The sunny disposition that
brings a smile to your face
As well as the heroic sense of justice
They may be a part of me,
but that's not all there is
That image of me
Has taken on a life of its own
Hey, wait up
Won't you be friends with me?
Let's shake hands, another self of mine
The wounds we cannot bear alone
The dangers that we keep hidden
We're all hiding them within
Standing ready to strike
The shadow lurking beneath the light
The muffled sounds coming from my lips
They make me feel that I am alive
It's a sign
Next Time
I'm Looking for Something Tastier than Me